1st grade student, 10 years old, can you name your high school?
1年生10歳 高校名とか言える?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘じゃない?
Sakura...High school name Oh, that's right.
桜...高校名 あ、そうなんだ
It's true.
本当なんだ
1 year?
1年?
How old is a first year student?
1年生 ってことは何歳なの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
You're young.
若いね
I would be happy if he was too young.
若い子すぎたら嬉しい
Well then, just out of curiosity.
じゃあさ、興味本位なんだけどさ、
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
Do you do any fun club activities?
楽しい 部活とかでやってたりするの?
Club activities... Don't you have a basketball club?
部活...バスケ部やってない?
It's the basketball club.
バスケ部なんだ
Is basketball fun?
バスケ楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいね
Since when have you been playing basketball?
いつからやってるのバスケは?
From high school to recently.
高校から 最近なんだ
Recently.
最近です
Can I film it?
映していいですか?
face.
顔
So it's cute, isn't it?
じゃあ可愛いですよね
Well then, it's starting to rain.
じゃあちょっと、雨降ってきたから
Maybe it's the rain man.
雨おとこかもしれない
Shall we go inside for a moment?
ちょっと中入りましょうか
for now.
とりあえず
Shall we go inside?
中入ろうか
Nice to meet you again.
改めまして
This is Yuka-chan.
ゆかちゃんです
yes.
はい
lol Your face is cute.
笑 顔可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You're really young, really.
めちゃめちゃ若いよね、本当に
Well, that's what I'm most concerned about.
で さ、一番気になってるんだけどさ、
It's on the back of Twitter, next to the at sign.
Twitterの裏側にさ、 アットマークの横にさ、
It's written like JK1, but...
JK1みたいにさ、書いてるんだけどさ、
What is that?
あれって何?
TRUE?
本当?
It's true.
本当です
TRUE?
本当?
It's true.
本当です
No, there are quite a lot.
いや、結構多いんですよ
It's not a scam though.
詐欺じゃないけどさ
A lot.
多くて
Really 1?
本当に1?
1st year student, 16 years old.
1年生、16歳
Can you tell me the name of your high school?
高校名とか言える?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘じゃない?
Sakurahigashi High School.
桜東高校です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's true.
本当なんだ
1 year?
1年?
I'm a first year student.
1年生です
So how old are you?
ってことは何歳なの?
10 years old.
10歳
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
You're young.
若いね
You young people are amazing, I'm so happy.
若い子すげえな、嬉しいです
Well then, just out of curiosity.
じゃあさ、興味本位なんだけどさ、
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
fun.
楽しい
Do you do any club activities?
部活とかでやってたりするの?
Don't you have a club or basketball club?
部活、バスケ部やってない?
It's the basketball club.
バスケ部なんだ
Is basketball fun?
バスケ楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Since when have you been playing basketball?
いつからやってるの、バスケは?
From high school.
高校から
It's been recent.
最近なんだ
Recently.
最近です
Is it hard to practice?
練習大変?
It's really hard.
めっちゃ大変です
That's right.
そうなんだ
What do you do in your free time?
休み時間とか何してるの?
I'm having a candy party with my friends.
友達とお菓子パーティしてます
Sweets party?
お菓子パーティ?
cute.
かわいい
Can we all bring some sweets?
みんなでお菓子持ち寄って?
that's right.
そうです
Are you going to eat sweets?
お菓子食べるんだ?
Eat.
食べます
Silently?
無言で?
No, I want something like Koibana.
いや、恋花とかしたい
Love flowers?
恋 花?
I'm going to fall in love with you.
恋花するんだ
Looks like a JK.
JKっぽいね
Does that mean you have a boyfriend now?
ってことは今、彼氏とかいるの?
No, my boyfriend.
いや、彼氏は
Is there someone you like?
好きな人いる?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Are you there?
いるの?
No, yeah.
いや、うん
It's a lighter version of something like a senior on the soccer club.
なんか、サッカー部の先輩とか、軽版だけど
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうなんだ
Eh, I can't help it.
え、なんかやけるな
That's nice.
いいな
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, what are you doing in law?
じゃあ、法学とか何してるの?
Japanese, karaoke.
国語、カラオケ
karaoke?
カラオケ?
karaoke.
カラオケ
I have an image of JK going to karaoke.
なんかイメージあるね、JKってカラオケに
Are there any subjects you're good at?
なんか、得意な科目とかあるの?
Like studying.
勉強とか
I'm good at subjects, oh, I'm good at Japanese.
得意な科目、あ、国語は得意
I'm good at this.
ここ得意なんだ
I'm good at Japanese.
国語は得意
It's the Japanese language.
国語なんだ
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Yes, I do.
うん、してます
Well, I contacted you on Twitter today.
じゃあさ、今日ツイッターで連絡したんだけどさ、
It felt like I was recruiting,
なんか、募集って感じだったからさ、
Do you usually do a lot?
普段結構やってんの?
That's what it is.
そういうこと
It may be rude though.
失礼かもしれないけど
Haven't you done it?
やってないの?
Usually, I don't do anything special.
普段は、なんか特にやってなくて
by chance?
たまたま?
accidental?
偶然?
today?
今日?
Ah, coincidence.
あ、偶然
lucky.
ラッキー
Why is it like that today?
なんで今日はあれなの?
Oh, my mobile phone has been a little weird this month.
あ、携帯台がちょっと、今月やばくて
Oh, a mobile stand?
あ、携帯台?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
What, don't you have a part-time job?
え、バイトとかしてない?
Oh, no, now.
あ、いや、してはいま
Oh, are you doing that?
あ、してるの?
I'm growing.
成長してます
What kind of system are you doing?
何系してるの?
Oh, I work in the food and beverage industry.
あ、飲食系やってて
where?
ど こ?
Acrylic up.
アクリルアップ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
He's a high school student.
高校生だね
But is the hourly wage low?
でも、時給低いか
I agree.
そうですね
Eh, but even though it's cheap, you can still pay for a mobile phone, right?
え、でも、低いとはいえさ、携帯台くらい払えるでしょ?
Oh, no,
あ、いや、
A game fan.
ゲ ームの派金師
It's amazing.
すげちゃって
It's now.
今時だね
What game are you playing?
何のゲームやってるの?
Um, uh, there's a guy who often does commercials.
あの、 あ、なんか、よくCMやってるやつが、
It's a rhythm game, right?
リズムゲームのやつでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
Did you spin the gacha?
ガチャ回しちゃった?
A lot.
だいぶ
I see.
そっか
That's kind of urgently needed.
それはちょっと急遽必要だね
Well, I haven't taken a bath, but today...
じゃあ、風呂はやってないけど、今日ちょっと、
I feel like this month is going to be a little crazy.
今月ちょっとヤバいからって感じで、
It feels like it's in a hurry.
急遽って感じだね
that's right.
そうです
Well, I'm kind of happy.
えー、なんか、嬉しい
It was lucky, lucky.
ラッキーラッキーだったね
Well then, there's something I'd like to talk about here.
じゃあさ、 まあ、ここ、ちょっと話したいのもあるしさ、
Well, let's move a little.
なんだからさ、ちょっと移動しよっか
Shall we go now?
そろそろ行こうか
Well, I understand.
ね、わかるよな
Well, let's go.
じゃあ、行こうか
You came to the hotel.
ホテル来ちゃったね
I can't go. I'm a high school student. Please come to the hotel.
行けないね、高校生だね、ホテル来ちゃって
Do you come often?
よく来るの?
No, it's not.
いや、じゃない
It just so happens that this is for hats.
これ、帽子用とかも、たまたまなんだもんね
that's right.
そうです
I patted her on the head because she was cute.
可愛いから頭なで、なしたの?
Are you nervous?
緊張しちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
Just a little longer, I can't hold back anymore
もうちょっとさ、我慢できないからさ、
Can I do what you said on Twitter?
ツイッターでさ、言ってたことをしてもらってもいい?
It may still be spinning.
まだ、回ってたりします
Yeah, it's spinning.
うん、回してるよ
I really wish the camera would stop.
カメラちょっと、さすがに止めてほしくて
But you said it was fine earlier.
でもさっき、いいって言ったじゃん
No, but the lift is cute.
いや、でも、リフトとか、可愛いから
No, it won't leak.
いや、流出しないよ、だって
It's just me.
俺だけだよ
No, but I really wish the camera would stop.
いや、でも、さすがにカメラ止めてほしくて
Is it that scary?
そんなに怖い?
No, hmm.
いや、うーん
Don't trust me?
信用できない?
I agree.
そうですね
I see.
そっか
Properly.
ちゃんと
That's right.
そっかそっか
I see.
なるほどね
Well then, as I said earlier,
じゃあさ、さっきも言ってたけどさ、
I'll increase it by hand compared to the original one,
元々のあれより、手で増やすから、
I think he said at first that he would come in second place, but
最 初は2位くらい、って言ってたと思うけど、
Increase the number by 1, please.
1位増やしてさ、ほら、 ピッて
Because it's a promise, because I said it earlier,
約束だから、さっき言ってたから、
Well, yes.
さ、はい
Promise me.
約束ね
No, just because it's gone means it's okay.
いや、しまったってことはいいってことだ
Well, that's good.
まあ、いいよね
Well then, come down here.
じゃあ、ここ、下に来て
Well then, let me get the camera.
じゃあ、ちょっとカメラ、取らせて
Have you ever touched it?
結構触ったことあるの?
No, no, no, no.
いや、ない、ない、ない
do not have?
ない?
It's getting hot.
熱くなってる
No, I like young girls, like JKs.
いや、さ、JKとかさ、若い子好きなの、
I like it.
好きなの
I think I fell in love a little.
ちょっと恋をしたみたいだけど
Are you playing?
弾いてる?
a little bit.
ちょっと
No, yeah.
いや、うん
Well then, take a look.
じゃあ、ちょっと、見てやって
You can see it hidden in your hand.
手に隠して見えるでしょ
Just touch it a little.
触るのは、ちょっと
why?
なんで?
No, just touch it.
いや、 ちょっと 触るだけじゃ
No, I mean stop.
いや、止めっていうか
what up?
どうした?
No, touching is a little different from a promise.
いや、約束と、 ちょっと違う、触るのは、
I didn't say that.
言ってなかった
Didn't you say that?
言ってなかった?
I didn't say that.
言ってなかった
I wanted to touch it, my brain went straight to it, and I wondered what it was like.
触りたくてさ、脳がすぐ行くし、 どうかなと思って
No, but.
いや、でも
Just touch me a little.
ちょっとだけ触らして
Hey, just a little bit, just a little bit.
ほら、ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
Let me touch you.
触らしてよ
That leg hurts a little.
そこのちょっと、足痛いでしょ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Just a little bit, then just touch me a little bit.
ちょっとだけ、じゃあ、ちょっとだけ触らしてよ
I've already touched it.
もう触っちゃってるし
If you touch me already, I'll add it again.
もう触らしてくれたら、 またプラスしちゃうか
I don't trust you.
信用ないよ
Plus, I don't trust it.
プラスすると信用ないよ
I'm still a little scared.
まだちょっと怖い
I see.
そうか
Well then, let's drop it first.
じゃあさ、最初に落としとくよ
Take it, take it.
受け取って、受け取って
Well then, that's fine.
じゃあ、いいでしょ
It's hard to find anything like this.
なかなかないよ、こんな
About age.
歳、ぐらい
Are you still on your way to your first trip?
まだ初行く途中?
I agree.
そうだね
It's the first year of high school.
高一だもんね
It's still to come.
まだ、これからだよ
Since when have you been wearing a bra?
いつからブラとかつけてんの?
Total students.
総学生
Over your clothes.
服の上からって
No, you didn't say over your clothes.
いや、服の上からって言ってないでしょ
What are you saying over your clothes?
服の上からなんて言ってんの?
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said.
って言ったけど
That's good.
いいよね
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said and received the money.
って言ってお金を受け取ってたから
I think you said earlier that it was over your clothes.
服の上からって、さっき言ってた気が
I didn't say it, I didn't say it.
言ってない、言ってない
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Ask me.
って聞いて
You didn't say that over your clothes.
服の上からって、言ってないでしょ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I heard.
って聞いたんだよ
Are your friends doing this?
友達とかもさ、こういうことしてんの?
No, I just don't understand.
いや、ちょっと分かんないから
That...
そっちは...
what?
何?
Why?
何で?
Why, why?
何で何で?
It's okay, I'll lie down here for a while.
いいじゃん、ちょっとここ寝転んだから
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I heard.
って聞いたんだから
I haven't heard of touching that part.
そこは触るって聞いてない
Did I just say no?
俺さっき断言した?
Just my chest.
胸だけって
No, no.
いや、やだ
You didn't say that.
言ってないでしょ
What do you want to do?
どうしたい?
Hey, it's coming out.
おい、出てるじゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Those who feel it quite a bit.
結構感じる方
Because I don't understand.
分かんないからさ
Don't take it off.
脱がさない
Well, just take it off and look at your panties.
じゃあ、脱がして、パンツ見るだけ
Just touch it from above your pants.
パンツの上から触るだけ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said.
って言ったじゃん
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what you said.
って言ってたでしょ
Don't take it off.
脱がすな
I'm touching you from above my pants.
パンツの上から触るんだよ
I said it.
言ったじゃん
That's a different story.
話違うし、それは
Don't take it off.
脱がすな
Don't want to take off your bottom?
下は脱ぎたくない?
Take off your top.
上を脱げて
So, can you take off your top?
じゃあ、上を脱げる?
Now, let's take off the top.
じゃあ、上を脱ごう
Take off your top.
上 を 脱 ご う
Here, hurray.
ほら、万歳
I didn't say take it off.
脱ぐとは言ってないから
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Well then, yes.
じゃあさ、はい
Now, show me your underwear.
これで、下着姿になって見せて
Please accept it.
受け取ってね
You want it, right?
欲しいんでしょ?
I want to help you.
助けてあげたいんだよ
Pants are pretty expensive, right?
パンツ結構支払いやばいんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
I'll give you that.
それあげるからさ
I'll give it to you, so let's take off your clothes and put on your underwear.
あげるから、服脱いで、下着姿になってみよう
It's not like we're sharing it.
別に共用してるわけじゃないからね
I just want to help with the money.
お金、協力してあげたいだけだから
Well then, let's stand there.
じゃあ、そこに立ってみようか
You can't see it, right?
見えないでしょ?
I'd like my money back.
お金返してもらおうよさ
Yeah.
うん
Hands, look, hands.
手、ほら、手
You're young.
若いね
It's chewy.
もちもちしてるね
Well then, let's touch it again.
じゃあ、もう一回、触ろうか
nice.
いいね
Look, melt, melt.
ほら、溶けて溶けて
It's embarrassing to be touched.
触られるの、恥ずかしいの
That's right
そっ
mosquito.
か
That's why.
だから ね
You told me to touch it at the beginning, right?
触るの、最初に言ってたでしょ?
Come to the front,
手前に来て、
I lean on that.
そ こにもたりかかってさ
Take a step back and make it in a short amount of time.
足引いて、短い時間に作って
Your skin looks beautiful.
肌、綺麗だね
It turns into salt.
塩になるからね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Leave your hands alone.
手、置いといて
I feel embarrassed.
恥ずかしいなって
If you touch it, it will make a sound.
触ったら声出てるね
He's been quite enthusiastic about it several times, isn't he?
何回かや、結構乗り気だって、そうでしょ
That's right.
そんなもんね
That may not be the case.
そんなことはないかも
Isn't that so?
そうでしょ
Because I'm touching it.
触ってるからさ
Well, not directly.
ちょっと、直接は
why?
なんで?
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
Directly, inside your clothes.
直接は、服の中は
I haven't gone, I haven't gone.
行ってない、行ってない
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
No, it was a different story at first.
いや、最初が違う話だったから
Should I give you the money now?
もう、お金渡したらいい?
No, but that's just clothes.
いや、でも、それは服のぐ
First, tell me you can touch me.
最初に、触っていいって言って
I'm touching something right now.
今、なんか触ってるんだよ
Then, on your clothes.
そっから、服の上で
It looks like it's being given separately.
別に渡してるみたいな
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
First, over your clothes.
最初、服の上から
Don't you want money?
お金欲しくないの?
No, money.
いや、お金は
If this happens, you want it to happen, right?
もし、これで起きたってことが欲しいんでしょ?
No, well.
いや、まあ
It's me.
私だもん
I haven't heard of you taking off your underwear.
下着取るのは、ちょっと聞いてない
Didn't I tell you to take off your underwear?
下着取るのは、言ってない?
We're together, right?
一緒でしょ
The clothes are the same, right?
服も一緒でしょ
We're together, right?
一緒でしょ
No, as expected.
いや、さすがに
As expected, the underwear.
さすがに、下着は
Do you want your money back?
お金返す?
Well then.
じゃあ
No, just like that.
いや、そーっと
Have fun.
楽しまして
It makes me laugh.
笑っちゃうよ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
I'm really enjoying it.
ほんと、楽しまして
It's a big deal.
せっかくなんだよ
You'll do this with your hands and mouth, but did you add money?
手と口で、こうしてもらうけど、 お金プラスしたの?
But it was a plus.
でも、 プ ラスしたんだよ
Yeah.
うん
I said touch it.
触るって言ってたよ
I added money, so that's about it.
お金プラスしたんだからさ、 そういう分ぐらい、
Isn't it nice to have a little fun?
ちょっと楽しましてくれていいんじゃない?
Return?
帰す?
No, that's it.
いや、それは
You don't like it, right?
嫌いでしょ?
picture?
え?
Sorry.
なめんなさい
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
A little more, okay, just a little more.
もうちょっと、いいでしょ、もうちょっとくらい
No, but that's a different story from the beginning.
いや、でも、最初と話違うです
That's why I said, you can touch me.
だから言ったじゃん、触っていいとか、
You said a lot of things.
いろいろ言ったじゃん
Did you receive the money?
お金受け取ったんでしょ?
I know it's difficult though.
難しいの分かるけどさ
Call me.
電話して
Is it visible?
映ってる?
I'm waiting for the camera.
カメラに自分待ちくるなのに
It's so beautiful.
す っごい綺麗だね
Lend me your legs and your hands for a moment.
ちょっと足、両手貸して
Yeah, lend me your hands.
うん、両手貸して
Hold a little bit in both hands.
両手にちょっとさ、やって挟んで
If you let me live with this, I'll be done with it.
これで生かしてくれたらもう終わりにいいよ
Oh, no, this is no good.
あ、駄目じゃん、これでいけない
I couldn't go.
いけなかった
Come on, it's still hurting here,
ちょっとさ、ここさ、まだ痛いからさ、
There are four pieces here once.
1回ここにさ、4つの枚なんで
A little bit from the left
左側からちょっとこっち
To.
に
Okay, use your butt.
よ い、お尻にしてね
You can't see it, there's still a little more to come.
見えないでしょ、まだもう少し付きなし
So let's take this out for a moment.
じゃあちょっとこれ抜いちゃおう
I'm not talking about pulling out the undercoat.
下毛抜くのは言ってない
You've outdone yourself.
上抜いてんじゃん
You've outdone yourself, right?
上抜いてんじゃん、いいでしょ
Okay, one more time.
いいでしょ、もう一回
But hey, it's way better than that.
でもさ、上抜いてんじゃん
It's good here too, right?
ここもいいってことでしょ
It's gone.
抜けてんじゃん
Eh, I'm pulling the strings.
え、糸引いてるよ
It's naughty, alright.
エッチだね、結構
Actually, I feel like I'm stuffy.
実 はムッツリみたいな
Look there.
見して、そこの
Shall I put it in there?
入れようか、そこに
Get through it, get out of it?
抜け通す、抜け取る?
I pushed and pulled.
押し引いた
Get out?
抜け取る?
Well, I have to show it to you.
じゃあ見せないとダメだよ
Push it open.
押し開いて
Make sure you can see it properly.
ちゃんと見えるようにして
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Have you never grown up there?
そこ生えたことないの?
It might not survive.
生えないかも
Come on, it's you.
生えさろ、お前か
Well then, I can't see it properly yet,
じゃあさ、そこまだちゃんと見えてないから、
Try opening it.
開いてみして
Huh, huh? Liar?
え、え、うそ?
Did you give the money?
お金渡したの?
Did you give it to him?
渡したでしょ?
Because that's what I want to see.
そこを見たいってことだからさ
Do it yourself, put your hands under your feet.
自分でさ、足の下から手回してさ
Is it a pin?
ピンかな?
Have you seen it yourself?
自分で見たことある?
Would you like to take a look?
見てみる?
It's wet.
濡れてるね
There is none.
無しいよ
Isn't it time to go in?
もう入るんじゃない?
I don't put it in at all.
入れるのは全然
You can't come in, right?
入れないでしょ
It's wet.
濡れてる
tight.
きつい